-[seagulls cawing]
-Are ya ready, kids?
-[海鸥啼叫]
-准备好了吗，孩子们？
[kids]
Aye-aye, Captain!
[孩子们]
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
[kids] Aye-aye, Captain!
[孩子们] 是啊，队长！
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
[kids]
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
[孩子们]
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
[Painty] ♪ Absorbent,
and yellow, and porous is he ♪
[油漆] ♪ 吸收性，
黄色、多孔的是他 ♪
[kids] ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
[孩子们] ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
[Painty] ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
[Painty] ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
[kids] ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
[孩子们] ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
[Painty] ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
[Painty] ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
-♪ SpongeBob SquarePants
-♪ Ready? ♪
-♪ 海绵宝宝
-♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
[all] ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
[全部] ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
[Painty]
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
[油漆]
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
[Painty laughing]
[佩蒂笑]
-[flute playing]
-[song ends]
-[长笛演奏]
-[歌曲结束]
-[waves lapping]
-[seagulls cawing]
-[海浪拍打]
-[海鸥啼叫]
[jaunty tropical music]
[欢快的热带音乐]
[Gary snoring]
[加里打鼾]
[spy music]
[间谍音乐]
[snoring continues]
[鼾声继续]
[SpongeBob grunts]
[海绵宝宝咕哝]
Hmm?
唔？
Perfect.
完美的。
-Ha! Huh?
-[phone ringing]
-哈！啊？
-[电话铃声]
Yes, who is it?
是的，是谁？
Hey, SpongeBob!
嘿，海绵宝宝！
Oh, hi, Patrick.
What's going on?
哦，嗨，帕特里克。
这是怎么回事？
Just getting dressed.
刚穿好衣服。
You wanna hang out?
你想出去玩吗？
Oh, I can't right now.
哦，我现在不能。
It's a big day for Gary.
这对加里来说是个重要的日子。
His snail-mitzvah already?
他的成年礼已经完成了吗？
No, that's tomorrow.
不，那是明天。
Today he's going to the V-E-T.
今天他要去参加 V-E-T。
Oh, I'd join you,
but I'm not dressed for the zoo.
哦，我愿意加入你，
但我没有穿好衣服去动物园。
The vet, Patrick.
兽医帕特里克.
Gary hates going to the vet
for his checkup,
加里讨厌去看兽医
为了他的检查，
so I always have to trick him
into the pet carrier.
所以我总是要欺骗他
放入宠物笼中。
[sniffing, chomping]
[嗅、咀嚼]
[happy meow]
[开心喵]
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
I left a trail of SnailPo treats
around the bathroom...
我留下了 SnailPo 零食的踪迹
浴室周围...
[meow]
[喵]
...down the stairs...
……下楼梯……
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
...through the living room...
...穿过客厅...
...and into the kitchen,
...然后走进厨房，
where he'll find a pile
of treats right inside...
他会在那里找到一堆
里面有零食……
[grunts] his pet carrier!
[咕哝]他的宠物笼！
Gotcha, Gary!
明白了，加里！
You still there, Patrick?
你还在吗，帕特里克？
Still here!
还在这里！
-[loud chewing]
-Patrick?
-[大声咀嚼]
-帕特里克？
Great plan, SpongeBob!
伟大的计划，海绵宝宝！
[vacuum noise]
[真空噪音]
Gary's gonna fall for it
for sure!
加里会爱上它
当然！
[burps, licking]
[打嗝，舔]
[meow]
[喵]
Oh, uh, hey, Gary.
哦，呃，嘿，加里。
-[dramatic sting]
-[meow]
-[戏剧性的刺痛]
-[喵]
Let me just...
让我...
[yowls angrily]
[愤怒地嚎叫]
Ah!
啊!
This is gonna be harder
than I thought.
这会更难
比我想象的要多。
More snail food, please!
再来点蜗牛食物吧！
Okay, Gary,
好吧，加里，
time for an innocent walk
with no ulterior motive.
无辜散步的时间
没有别有用心。
[hisses, yowls]
[嘶嘶声，嚎叫声]
I'm sorry, Gary,
对不起，加里，
but you need to...
see your doctor!
但你需要...
看你的医生！
[loud thud]
[巨响]
[blows raspberry]
[吹覆盆子]
Oh, barnacles.
哦，藤壶。
Perhaps I'll need a ruse
that's even rusier.
也许我需要一个诡计
那更生锈了。
[SpongeBob grunting]
[海绵宝宝咕哝]
[door creaks]
[门吱吱作响]
Oh, Gary, you're here!
哦，加里，你来了！
Forget that silly veterinarian!
忘记那个愚蠢的兽医吧！
I booked a big tropical vacation
just for the two of us!
我预订了一个热带假期
只为我们两个人！
[sheepish laugh]
[羞涩的笑声]
Won't it be nice to just
get away for awhile and relax?
就这样不是很好吗
离开一段时间放松一下？
So just get into that vacation
carriage and we can take off!
所以就进入那个假期吧
马车我们可以起飞了！
Come on, Gary,
just get in that pet carrier...
来吧，加里，
只要进入那个宠物笼...
-[angry meow]
-Oh, hi, Gary.
-[生气喵]
-哦，嗨，加里。
-[hisses]
-Whoa!
-[嘶嘶声]
-哇！
Gary! Let me out, boy!
加里！放我出去吧，小子！
Be a good snail!
做一只好蜗牛！
[French narrator]
Two weeks later...
[法语旁白]
两周后...
-[meow]
-Okay, okay, I'll admit it.
-[喵]
-好吧好吧，我承认。
I feel rejuvenated. Hmph!
我感觉自己又恢复了活力。哼！
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
Look, Gary!
This letter came for you!
看，加里！
这封信是写给你的！
It's an invitation
to a big party
这是一个邀请
去参加一个大型聚会
at Snail Fail's house!
在蜗牛失败家！
He is the most famous snail
in town,
他是最有名的蜗牛
在城里，
and you're his VIP!
而你就是他的 VIP！
Oh? [nervous laugh]
哦？ [紧张的笑声]
-[angry meow]
-[horn honks]
-[生气喵]
-[喇叭鸣响]
He even sent a limousine!
他甚至还派了一辆豪华轿车！
Meow!
喵！
[British accent]
After you, my good snail...
[英国口音]
在你之后，我的好蜗牛……
Pretty fancy, huh?
很花哨，是吧？
A pity we'll have to cancel
that vet appointment,
遗憾的是我们不得不取消
那个兽医预约，
but there's no way
we could miss--
但没有办法
我们可能会错过——
Patrick?!
帕特里克？！
Yeah, I'm pretty hard to miss.
是的，我很难错过。
Hey!
嘿！
-Gary! Uh...
-[meow]
-加里！呃...
-[喵]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[metal smashing]
[金属粉碎]
[meow]
[喵]
-Ouch.
-Ow...
-哎哟。
-噢...
[TV Announcer] And now
back toSnails of Our Lives.
[电视播音员] 现在
回到我们生活中的蜗牛。
[kissing sounds]
[接吻声]
[sentimental piano music]
【感伤的钢琴曲】
Hmm. If I can't convince Gary
by lying to him,
唔。如果我不能说服加里
通过对他撒谎，
I'll have to convince him
with brutal honesty!
我得说服他
带着残酷的诚实！
Here comes... the guilt trip.
来了……内疚之旅。
[TV Announcer] Next time
onSnails of Our Lives...
[电视播音员] 下次
关于我们生活中的蜗牛...
-[female snail] Meow?
-[male snail] Meow.
-【母蜗牛】喵？
-【雄性蜗牛】喵。
[sniffling]
[抽鼻子]
Gary, I'm begging you.
Please go to the veterinarian!
加里，我求你了。
请去看兽医！
I'm worried sick about you!
我真替你担心死了！
Do you want me to be sick, Gary?
你想让我生病吗，加里？
Are you trying to send me
to an early grave?!
你想发给我吗
早早进入坟墓？！
Oh! Gah!
哦！嘎！
I would do anything
for you, Gary!
我愿意做任何事
为了你，加里！
Anything!
任何事物！
[crying]
[哭泣]
[wailing]
[哀号]
[award announcer] And the winner
for best acting is...
[颁奖嘉宾] 获奖者
最佳表演是...
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
Oh! Oh, my! Thank you!
哦！哦，天哪！谢谢你！
It was an honor
just to be nominated.
这是一种荣幸
只是为了被提名。
If you had told me
eleven minutes ago
如果你告诉我
十一分钟前
that little old SpongeBob would
win an award for anything, I--
那个小老海绵宝宝会
赢得任何奖项，我——
Wait a minute!
等一下！
Gary? Double barnacles!
加里？双藤壶！
That sneaky snail
got away again.
那只狡猾的蜗牛
又逃走了。
That's it!
就是这样！
I am taking Gary to the vet...
我要带加里去看兽医...
by any means necessary.
通过任何必要的手段。
No more Mr. Nice Sponge.
不再是好海绵先生了。
[adventurous music]
[冒险音乐]
Time for a snail hunt!
是时候去捉蜗牛了！
La la la la la!
啦啦啦啦啦！
Hmm...
唔...
[lick] Still warm.
[舔]还是暖和的。
[gasp] A fresh kill...
[喘息]新鲜的杀戮......
[munching]
[咀嚼]
Aha! Gotcha!
啊哈！明白了！
[surprised meow]
[惊讶喵]
[angry yowl]
[愤怒的咆哮]
[meow]
[喵]
I see you've fallen
into one of the many traps
我看到你已经堕落了
陷入众多陷阱之一
I've set around the house.
我已经在房子周围布置好了。
Whoa!
哇！
-[shouting]
-[angry meows]
-[喊叫]
-[愤怒的喵喵声]
[steam hissing]
[蒸汽嘶嘶声]
[drain gurgling]
[排水沟咕噜声]
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
Hey, a little privacy please?
嘿，请有点隐私吗？
Vet time!
兽医时间！
[yowls]
[嚎叫]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[laser buzzing]
[激光嗡嗡声]
[hypnotized meow]
[催眠喵]
Meow!
喵！
That's it, Gary, follow the dot.
就这样，加里，跟着点走。
Let's just think rationally
here, Gary. Heh.
我们理性思考一下
在这里，加里。呵呵。
[yowl]
[号叫]
-[angry meowing]
-[shouting]
-[愤怒的喵喵声]
-[喊叫]
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
[Spaghetti Western
showdown music]
[意大利式西部片
对决音乐]
[rousing music playing]
[振奋人心的音乐]
[angry meow]
[生气喵]
Ooh! [inhales]
哦！ [吸气]
Meow!
喵！
Gotcha!
明白了！
[squeaky punches landing]
[吱吱作响的拳头落地]
[veterinarian]
Mr. SquarePants?
[兽医]
方裤先生？
You may bring in your snail now.
你现在可以把你的蜗牛带进来了。
[muffled growling]
[低沉的咆哮声]
Goodness, Gary!
What healthy teeth you have!
天哪，加里！
你的牙齿多么健康啊！
[chomp, munching]
[咀嚼，咀嚼]
Ptoo!
噗！
Gary, be nice
to the kind doctor!
加里，乖一点
致善良的医生！
Oh, that's quite alright,
Mr. SquarePants.
噢，那完全没问题，
方裤先生。
I know exactly how to handle
vicious snails.
我清楚地知道如何处理
恶毒的蜗牛。
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
With a...
与一个...
lollipop!
棒糖！
Meow?
喵？
All done.
全部完成。
That's it?
就是这样？
Yep. That's a medical lollipop
是的。这是医用棒棒糖
full of all the vitamins
and vaccinations
富含所有维生素
和疫苗接种
a growing snail needs.
成长中的蜗牛需要。
See, Gary?
看到了吗，加里？
That wasn't so bad after all.
毕竟那还不算太糟糕。
Well, thanks, Doctor.
嗯，谢谢，医生。
See ya next year!
明年见！
Oh, you can't leave,
Mr. SquarePants.
噢，你不能离开，
方裤先生。
You're covered in bites
and scratches.
你被咬伤了
和划痕。
[nervous laugh] Uh, yeah,
[紧张的笑声] 呃，是的，
Gary did get a little rough
on the way over here.
加里确实有点粗暴
正在来这里的路上。
I guess I'll take a lollipop,
too!
我想我会带一根棒棒糖
也！
Oh, no,
sponges don't get lollipops.
哦，不，
海绵不能得到棒棒糖。
You don't want to get infected,
so you'll need
你不想被感染，
所以你需要
the full treatment!
全面治疗！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[sigh]
[叹]
I don't wanna go to the vet!
我不想去看兽医！
[crying]
[哭泣]
[lively tropical music]
[活泼的热带音乐]
[male fitness instructor]
And five! And four!
【男健身教练】
还有五个！还有四个！
And three!
And two! And one!
还有三个！
还有两个！还有一个！
Great job!
干得好！
You've finished your warm-up.
你已经完成了热身。
Now pop in another quarter and
let's get to the real workout!
现在弹出另一个四分之一
让我们开始真正的锻炼吧！
Whew!
哇！
Just the warm-up today,
Mr. Pelican machine.
今天只是热身，
鹈鹕先生机器。
And now for my next workout...
现在我的下一次锻炼......
[deep inhale, blows]
[深吸气，吹气]
The speed bag!
速度包！
What?!
什么？！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Yes!
是的！
[groans]
[呻吟]
Feel the burn!
感受灼烧感！
Nyah! Burning!
呀！燃烧！
Burning!
燃烧！
[zany laugh]
[滑稽的笑声]
Ugh!
啊!
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊！
Today, I am pushing it
to the limit!
今天我就来推一下
到极限！
[groans] Whew!
[呻吟] 哇！
Whew!
哇！
Shoo!
嘘！
Whew!
哇！
[bones cracking]
[骨头碎裂]
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
Time for a new personal best!
是时候创造新的个人最好成绩了！
[straining]
[紧张]
[groans]
[呻吟]
Half... way... there... !
一半……一半……那里……！
[straining]
[紧张]
[slow-motion groan]
[慢动作呻吟]
-[thud]
-[car horn honks]
-[砰]
-[汽车喇叭鸣响]
-[bell ringing]
-[explosion]
-[铃声响起]
-[爆炸]
[engine revs]
[发动机转速]
[straining]
[紧张]
I'm pinned!
我被钉住了！
Okay, SpongeBob,
you can figure this out.
好吧，海绵宝宝，
你可以弄清楚这一点。
Just keep calm!
保持冷静！
Hmm. Can't see anything.
唔。什么也看不见。
I know! I'll let my foot fingers
do the walking.
我知道！我会让我的脚手指
走路。
There's gotta be something
in here that can help me.
一定有什么东西
在这里可以帮助我。
Hmm. Nope, too toothy.
唔。不行，太露齿了。
Too spicy.
太辣了。
Too crowbar-y.
太撬棍了。
Ow! Too snappy!
噢！太快了！
Ooh!
哦！
[chomp]
[咀嚼]
Oh, no good!
哦，不好！
What am I gonna... [gasp]
我要做什么...[喘气]
Gary will save me!
加里会救我的！
Gary!
加里！
-Come in here, buddy!
-[meows]
-进来吧，伙计！
-[喵]
I need you!
我需要你！
[annoyed meow]
[生气喵]
Please, Gary?
拜托，加里？
Oh, Garebear...
哦，加贝尔...
[French narrator]
One hour later...
[法语旁白]
一小时后...
Come on, Gary... I need you.
来吧，加里……我需要你。
Meow?
喵？
Oh, Gary!
Thank goodness!
哦，加里！
谢天谢地！
I'm trapped beneath this bar.
我被困在这个酒吧下面了。
Come get it off me, please.
请过来把它从我身上拿下来。
Hurry! Yeah!
匆忙！是的！
You're doing it, Gary!
你正在做，加里！
Just a little closer...
再近一点...
Uh, what are you doing, buddy?
呃，你在做什么，伙计？
-[snoring]
-Aww.
-[打鼾]
-哇。
Poor little guy's
all tuckered out.
可怜的小家伙
全部都被掏空了。
[meowing, snoring]
[喵喵声，打鼾声]
Uh, not sure this is
helping me though.
呃，不确定这是
不过帮助我。
Wait! Gary always keeps
等待！加里始终坚持
a journaling pen
inside his shell!
日记笔
在他的壳里！
[muttering]
[嘀咕]
Eureka!
尤里卡！
"Send help.
“发送帮助。
I've become trapped under my
weights in my upstairs gym.
我已经被困在我的
在我楼上的健身房里举重。
My name is SpongeBob.
我的名字是海绵宝宝。
My snail's name is Gary.
我的蜗牛叫加里。
Gary is here too,
but he fell asleep,
加里也来了
但他睡着了，
so I'm relying on you,
kind stranger."
所以我依赖你
善良的陌生人。”
Soon it'll be just a matter
of time before I'm rescued!
很快这将只是一个问题
距离我获救还有一段时间！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Oh, come on!
哦，来吧！
[bottle whooshing]
[瓶子嘶嘶作响]
[cries out]
[喊叫]
Hey! What's the big idea?
嘿！有什么大创意？
Ohh! Alright, who threw this?
哦！好吧，这是谁扔的？
Oh!
哦！
That does it, wisenheimer!
就这样，威森海默！
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
Bikini Bottom Police Department.
比基尼警察局。
How may I protect and serve?
我该如何保护和服务？
[unintelligible
angry muttering]
[难以理解
愤怒的嘀咕]
An assault!
袭击！
Not in our town!
我们镇上没有啊！
We'll send a squad boat
right away!
我们会派出一艘小艇
马上！
To the cop mobile!
到警察手机！
[loud squeaking]
[大声吱吱声]
Hit it.
击中它。
[mimics siren sound]
[模仿警报声]
Ha-ha! You hear that,
mysterious miscreant?
哈哈！你听到了，
神秘的恶棍？
You are so...
你真是……
Saved!
得救了！
Oh, Gary, I'm saved!
哦，加里，我得救了！
[snoring, meowing]
[打鼾、喵喵声]
[police radio chatter]
[警察电台喋喋不休]
Uh, what was that address again?
呃，那个地址又是什么？
-Oh, it's... Squidward!
-Squidward!
-哦，这是……章鱼哥！
-章鱼哥！
Man, that guy's always calling.
伙计，那个家伙总是打电话来。
Yeah, last time
it was because of a trespassing
是的，上次
这是因为非法侵入
sea-fly in his living room!
海蝇在他的客厅里！
Oh, shrimp, there he is!
哦，虾，他来了！
Duck!
鸭子！
Over here, officers!
这边，军官们！
What-- What the--?
什么——什么——？
Well, they did say they were
gonna send a squad boat.
嗯，他们确实说过他们是
会派出一艘小艇。
[blows raspberry] Idiots.
[吹覆盆子]白痴。
Oh... they didn't stop.
哦……他们没有停下来。
Must knock bottle out of window!
必须把瓶子打出窗外！
Ooh, finally I can put
these gym tools to use!
哦，终于可以放了
这些健身工具好用！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Hmm. Nothing left to throw.
唔。没有什么可以扔的。
[gasp] Except... Gary.
[喘气]除了……加里。
Sorry, buddy,
you're my only hope.
对不起，哥们，
你是我唯一的希望。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Okay, Gary,
好吧，加里，
try to knock the bottle
out of the window.
尝试敲瓶子
窗外。
[snoring, meowing]
[打鼾、喵喵声]
Oh, I've really done it now!
哦，我现在真的做到了！
All hope is lost!
所有的希望都破灭了！
I've tried everything
and failed!
我已经尝试了一切
并失败了！
All conceivable chances
of escape, exhausted!
所有能想到的机会
逃跑的时候，累死了！
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
Oh yeah, the phone!
哦，对了，电话！
Sweet Neptune, help me!
亲爱的海王星，帮帮我吧！
I'm pinned under weights
in my home gym!
我被重压压住
在我家的健身房里！
[radio announcer]
That's correct!
[电台播音员]
没错！
The song of the day is
"Sweet Neptune, Help Me!
当天的歌曲是
“亲爱的海王星，救救我吧！
I'm Pinned Under Weights
in My Home Gym,"
我被重压压垮
在我的家庭健身房，”
by Scalawag and the Sea Dogs!
作者：无赖与海狗！
Listener, you just won
$1,000!
听众，你刚刚赢了
1,000 美元！
I-I... I did?
我-我...我做到了？
Yeah! Ifyou can get down here
是的！如果你能下来这里
to the station
in the next 10 minutes!
到车站
在接下来的 10 分钟内！
K-DEEP, we play the hits!
K-DEEP，我们演奏热门歌曲！
No! Don't hang up!
不！别挂断！
-[disconnect tone]
-Oh, fiddlesticks!
-[断开连接音]
-哦，小提琴手！
Hm, if I randomly hit numbers
with my toe,
嗯，如果我随机击中数字
用我的脚趾，
I'm sure to call somebody.
我肯定会打电话给某人。
[muttering]
[嘀咕]
-Hello?
-Larry!
-你好？
-拉里！
I need your help.
I'm trapped under my weights!
我需要你的帮助。
我被我的重压困住了！
I wish I could help you, bro,
but...
我希望我能帮助你，兄弟
但是...
Larry's got problems
of his own.
拉里有问题
他自己的。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[phone rings]
[电话铃声]
Eh, hello?
呃，喂？
-[ringing continues]
-Hello?
-[铃声继续]
-你好？
[heavy breathing]
Yes, what is it?
[粗重的呼吸]
是的，那是什么？
Trapped, you say?
你说被困住了？
All alone?
一个人吗？
And you can't move?
而你却不能动？
[chuckles] That sounds...
[笑]听起来……
excruciating.
令人难以忍受。
[heavy breathing through phone]
[电话里传来粗重的呼吸声]
Ew! Uh, sorry, wrong number!
呃！呃，抱歉，号码打错了！
Oh, that's not good.
哦，这样不好。
[French narrator]
Many hours later.
[法语旁白]
许多小时后。
H-help... help...
呼、救命……救命……
[both] There's no one who can
help you now, SpongeBob.
[双双] 没有人可以
现在就帮助你吧，海绵宝宝。
[all] No one!
[全部] 没有人！
No... my friends will find me.
不...我的朋友会找到我的。
How?
如何？
They don't even know
where you are.
他们甚至不知道
你在哪里。
But we know where you are,
big silly!
但我们知道你在哪里
大傻！
We'll be your friends
to the end of your days.
我们会成为你的朋友
直到你生命的尽头。
Hee hee hee
hee hee hee.
嘻嘻嘻
嘻嘻嘻。
[creepy laughter]
[令人毛骨悚然的笑声]
[creepy laughter intensifies]
[令人毛骨悚然的笑声加剧]
[honking laugh]
[喇叭笑声]
[deranged laughter]
[疯狂的笑声]
-[doorbell rings]
-A visitor?
-[门铃响了]
-访客？
Oh, I'm saved!
哦，我得救了！
[strained] Come in.
[紧张]进来吧。
[whimsical music]
[异想天开的音乐]
Hello?
你好？
SpongeBob?
Are you home?
海绵宝宝？
你在家吗？
Up here.
上这里。
I'm up... here.
我起来了……在这里。
I don't hear anything.
我什么也没听到。
The coast is clear!
海岸清澈见底！
-Oh, boy!
-[shouting]
-哦，孩子！
-[喊叫]
This is gonna be
the best surprise party
这将会是
最好的惊喜派对
SpongeBob's ever had!
海绵宝宝曾经有过！
You hear that, Gary?
你听到了吗，加里？
Soon I'll be free.
很快我就会自由了。
[snoring, meowing]
[打鼾、喵喵声]
[cheering and laughing]
[欢呼和大笑]
Eee!
哎呀！
-Hooray!
-Arrr!
-万岁！
-啊啊！
[faintly] H... H... Help!
[微弱地]呼……呼……救命啊！
[gulps air]
[倒吸一口空气]
I'm... upstairs.
我……在楼上。
[chattering]
[喋喋不休]
I wonder what kind of fun stuff
is up there?
我想知道有什么好玩的东西
在上面吗？
[exhales]
[呼气]
Saved.
已保存。
What are ye doing, lads?
小伙子们，你们在做什么？
Keep your mirth and mayhem
downstairs
保持你的欢乐和混乱
楼下
in the designated party area.
在指定的聚会区域。
[both] Aye, aye, Captain.
[两人] 是的，是的，船长。
[SpongeBob, weakly]
Wait! Come back!
[海绵宝宝，有气无力]
等等！回来！
Oh, it's no use.
哦，没用的。
They can't hear my voice.
他们听不到我的声音。
But maybe they can hear
my foot's voice.
但也许他们能听到
我的脚的声音。
[pops]
[流行音乐]
[stomping]
[跺脚]
[loud chatter]
[大声喧哗]
-[foot stomping]
-Quiet!
-[跺脚]
-安静！
Do you hear that?
你听到了吗？
-[rhythmic stomping]
-Ooh! I know this shanty!
-[有节奏的跺脚]
-哦！我知道这个棚屋！
♪ Sweet Neptune, help me
♪ 亲爱的海王星，帮助我
♪ I'm pinned under weights
in my home gym ♪
♪ 我被重压压住了
在我家的健身房里♪
♪ By Jove, by Jim
I tried to be trim ♪
♪ 乔夫，吉姆
我努力让自己变得苗条起来♪
♪ I'm pinned under weights
in my home gym ♪
♪ 我被重压压住了
在我家的健身房里♪
♪ I tried to get buff
but it wasn't enough ♪
♪ 我试图获得增益
但这还不够♪
♪ When the weight had its way,
the going got tough ♪
♪ 当重量发挥作用时，
事情变得艰难♪
-♪ No shimmy or shim
-♪ My quivering limbs ♪
-♪ 无摆振或垫片
-♪ 我的四肢颤抖 ♪
♪ Pinned under weights
in my home gym ♪
♪ 被重物压住
在我家的健身房里♪
♪ So, hoist the barbells
over lads ♪
♪ 所以，举起杠铃
超越小伙子♪
♪ They'll sink
before they swim ♪
♪ 他们会沉没的
在他们游泳之前♪
Uh-oh.
I knew I should have paid extra
呃哦。
我知道我应该支付额外费用
for the shanty-proof floor!
用于防棚地板！
-Whoa!
-[singing stops]
-哇！
-[歌声停止]
[harmonica flourish]
[口琴蓬勃发展]
Surprise!
惊喜！
...and that's why I was almost
late for work this morning.
...这就是为什么我几乎
今天早上上班迟到了。
Stop your lollygagging
and get to work!
停止你的棒棒糖
开始工作吧！
Aye, aye, Mr. Krabs, sir.
是的，是的，蟹老板先生，先生。
[grunting, muttering]
[咕哝，咕哝]
Order up!
赶快下单吧！
[laughs]
[笑]
[end theme music playing]
[结束主题音乐播放]